# **Augusto Omena**

Full Stack Developer

## **Summary**

I have worked as a Full-Stack developer, through internship and self-taught projects, I have built a foundation in web development and problem solving. I have been working as a freelancer for the last 4 months. My specialty includes .Net and Angular.

## **Relevant Experience**

Full Stack Developer · Builtcode April 2024 - Present

• Full Stack Development: Responsible for developing and implementing new features in internal products and partner solutions using .NET and Angular.

Developer Internship · PMAR Set 2023 - Apr 2024

- Website Development: Developed responsive websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- .NET Projects: Gained substantial experience in web development, building simple APIs and websites with the .NET framework.

Naval Industrial Electrician Apprentice · Firjan Mai 2022 – Mai 2023

• Windows Applications: Developed solutions using .Net, Java, and C++.

augusto.n.omena@gmail.com

S +55 (24) 98102-1079

in linkedin.com/in/augusto-omena

github.com/AugustoOmena

<u>augustoomena.github.io/Portfolio</u>

#### **Skills**

**Programming Languages** 

C#, Java, Kotlin, Typescript, HTML, CSS

**Libraries & Frameworks** 

.Net, Angular, Spring Boot

**Tools & Platforms** 

Git, GitHub, Azure DevOps, Docker, SQL

## **Selected Project**

### **Internal medicine**

This is a simple project I did to demonstrate my skills with angular and .Net, a full-fledged medical clinic Backoffice.

#### Education

Centro Universitário Senac

Bachelor's degree, Technology in Systems Analysis and Development (June 2022 - December 2024)